# Tanvi Sachdeva

Full Stack

# Contact

**Address** 

Pune, India, 411057

**Phone** 

916 858 8710

E-mail

sachdevatanvi2311@gmail.c om

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sachdevatanvi2311/

**www** 

https://tanvisachdeva.githu b.io/tanviprofile.html

#### **Skills**

**Javascript** 

**Angular** 

.NET Full Stack

Scrum

Agile

C#

Leadership and Management

Azure

Project Management

**Typescript** 

8+ years of experience in leading and managing project delivery with significant experience as an individual contributor.

Tech stack - JavaScript, typescript, Angular, .NET, C#, WebApi, React, Agile and Azure AZ900 certified and more than willing to upskill in newer technologies should the project require. Have international experience of working in France on client side.

# **Work History**

2022-04 -Current

#### **Full Stack Lead**

Accenture India

- WebApi, C#, REST, GIT, Typescript, React, Redux,
   Balsamiq, Adobe XD, Google cloud, object oriented programming, Agile, Scrum ceremonies
- Develop, build, review and test frontend and backend software solutions and work with other developers and businesses to propose high-quality solutions to meet business goals.
- Confident in working independently or in a team in a deadline driven environment with quality deliverables.
- Strong communication and organizational skills with an ability to thrive in a fast-paced production deadline-driven environment both internal and client facing.
- Ability to solve complex development problems and produce the highest quality code while striving to push technical boundaries of online applications
- Ability to work quickly while maintaining strong attention to detail and accuracy while adhering to W3C and accessibility guidelines.
- Strong attention to detail and understanding of UI concepts to provide perspective on front and backend technologies and their overall impact on the creative process.

2019-06 -2022-04

#### **Technical Lead**

Sopra Steria India Limited

 Client - European multinational aerospace leader ( Have international experience of working in France on client side) HTML

CSS

Mongodb

SQL

Object Oriented Programming

React

**Algorithms** 

- Javascript, Angular, .NET Webapi, Agile, GIT, IIS, Mongodb
- Lead and performed end to end delivery of web applications starting from requirement understanding to implementation to deployment.
   Contribute to end-to-end codebase of application including rich frontend, thoughtful web APIs, and well-designed databases
- Participate in all scrum ceremonies. Closely worked with Product owners/client/business in scoping and estimation of user stories during PI planning.
- Mentored junior team members who are on a technical career path and are interested in becoming future technical leads and engineers.

#### 2018-06 -2019-06

# **Lead Engineer**

HCL Technologies Limited

- Client American multinational technology leader
- ASP.net MVC, GIT, Azure, jQuery, Ajax, JavaScript, CSS
- Investigating bugs in software application based on technical expertise and developing solutions in accordance with quality accredited standards.
- Mentored team members on technical front so that quality code is delivered with minimal postproduction bugs/issues.
- Full understanding of web Accessibility including knowledge of WCAG 3.0
- Effectively manage scope and client expectations on individual assignments.
- Work with Agile team to deliver applications iteratively, and incorporate feedback into future iterations.

### 2015-08 -2018-04

# **Product Integration Engineer**

EdgeVerve Systems Limited

- Client American multinational telecom leader
- .NET MVC, SQL, Jquery, Javascript, Angular
- Analyze business problems, develop technology solutions to those problems and manage project through its lifecycle.

- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Providing timely deliverables to client, solving post production bugs/issues were handled.

2014-09 -2015-07

# **Systems Engineer**

Infosys Limited

- Client American multinational telecom leader
- Full stack developer
- C#, .NET, Angular JS, SQL

# **Education**

2010-08 -2014-07

# Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science And Engineering

Rajasthan Technical University
My bachelor's is equivalent to 4 years Canadian
Bachelor's degree certified through Education
Credential Assessment done by University of Toronto

# **Certifications**

2021-05	AZ-900 Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals
2021-06	AZ-104 Microsoft Certified Azure Administrator